module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Who directed the Dune movie released in 1984?",
      a: 'Andrei Tarkovsky',
      b: 'Ridley Scott',
      c: 'David Lynch',
      d: 'Alejandro Jodorwosky',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is in the Gom Jabbar?',
      a: 'Pain',
      b: 'Fear',
      c: 'Truth',
      d: 'Knowledge',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Sting plays which character in the 1984 Dune movie?',
      a: 'Beast Rabban',
      b: 'Feyd-Rautha',
      c: 'Vladimir Harkonnen',
      d: 'Wellington Yueh',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Due to the prohibition of "thinking machines", human computers known as _____ were created.',
      a: 'Bene Gesserit',
      b: 'Fremen',
      c: 'Bene Tleilax',
      d: 'Mentats',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Kyle Machlachan (so handsome), plays which character in the 1984 Dune movie?',
      a: 'Thufir Hawat',
      b: 'Paul Atriedes',
      c: 'Duncan Idaho',
      d: 'Gurney Halleck',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following nomadic peoples are the Fremen NOT based on?',
      a: 'Bedouin',
      b: 'Blackfeet Nation',
      c: 'Ainu',
      d: 'San People',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Dune is the nickname for what planet?',
      a: 'Arrakis',
      b: 'Geidi Prime',
      c: 'Salusa Secundus',
      d: 'Caladan',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the only character to appear in all 6 of Frank Herbert's original Dune novels?",
      a: 'Gurney Halleck',
      b: 'Leto Atriedes',
      c: 'Miles Teg',
      d: 'Duncan Idaho',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The "Old man of the desert" is a reference to what?',
      a: 'The Spice Melange',
      b: 'Shai-Hulud',
      c: "Muad'dib",
      d: 'Liet-Kynes',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'The soundtrack for the 1984 Dune movie was written by Brian Eno and ________',
      a: 'Toto',
      b: 'A-Ha',
      c: 'Depeche Mode',
      d: 'Duran Duran',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};